<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>samadhiBot</title>
  <subtitle>samadhiBot ministry of information</subtitle>
  <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/</id>
  <link href="http://one.samadhibot.com/"/>
  <link href="http://one.samadhibot.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2015-05-29T07:02:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>समाधिBot</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>I Call It the Bewilder-Frog</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/05/29/i-call-it-the-bewilder-frog/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/05/29/i-call-it-the-bewilder-frog/</id>
    <published>2015-05-29T07:02:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-05-29T08:11:16-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-05-29-i-call-it-the-bewilder-frog-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What would you call this new piece of artwork?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Well… it’s a new made up thing I made. I call it the bewilder-frog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: The bewilder-frog? I like that name!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: It wears a mask because it tries to hide its face, because its face doesn’t really look
like a normal frog, so it wears a mask all the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Is its face bewildering? Or is it a total mystery??&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Well… its face is kind of like grey black white colored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Oh… not a normal frog face at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Uh-uh. And usually they’re covered with scratches and bite marks, because when something
sees it, it automatically gets so frightened and mad at the same time, even though it didn’t do
anything. So it just bites, scratches, and does whatever it wants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: I’ve seen animals act like that. Tell me about the cape. Why does he wear a cape?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Well, they don’t really like being on the ground for that long, because they just don’t
really like any animals around. And so they climb up a tree, jump, and they kind of glide for a
moment, and then they land on another tree.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Does the cape help them glide?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah, it kind of helps them glide, because they eat like once a month or once a week.
They’re not really that much weighted. They’re light weighted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;div class="image"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-05-29-i-call-it-the-bewilder-frog-2-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Now tell me about the mask.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Oh the mask. The mask was made like three days ago, but it took a long time. It took the
whole day until the evening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Really?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah. That was the first mask I made. Then I didn’t think it would look good, so I
switched to making another mask, but it got torn because Zahra was messing with it, and it
didn’t really work out right. So I picked that one up and I thought, “This might work out!” So I
just kept cutting until it was all done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then I &lt;em&gt;did&lt;/em&gt; like the drawings. The black things sticking down from its lower jaw,
they’re vangs, and there’s vangs at the top. They use vangs for poisonous snakes, ‘cos snakes
don’t really like to interact with other vanged creatures or snakes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It has three eyes because it can see better, hunt better, and it’s so it can see up and down.
So if there’s a big bird swooping down, it can look up. And the two extra eyes, they’re for
looking sideways and forwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: That one at the top, in the middle, in mystical traditions that can represent spiritual
vision, or inner vision. Does this frog have that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah. The reason why it has three layers it’s because it can close in its eyes at the
thing that’s right above it so it can see better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And there’s that nose thingy because it likes to pretend it’s a big cat. That’s the reason why
it has a mask on its face, it pretends to be a three-eyed lion. It tries to pretend it’s a lion.
Everyone knows that it’s bad to mess with a male lion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>This Page is About Crocodiles</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/05/27/this-page-is-about-crocodiles/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/05/27/this-page-is-about-crocodiles/</id>
    <published>2015-05-27T09:15:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-05-27T09:31:49-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-05-27-this-page-is-about-crocodiles-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: This page is about crocodiles. This little one is um… it’s one of the… you know those
crocodiles, those big crocodiles… yes this is a saltwater crocodile. This is a marine crocodile
that lives back in time. This is what they start off looking like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Ahh…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: This is a black cayman. And this is just a normal one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Okay. How come… is the marine — or the saltwater crocodile — is that a baby one?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah this is kind of what a baby one looks like. &lt;em&gt;Annnd&lt;/em&gt; it’s kind of mad at this
guy because it’s been kicking it with its back foot. So it’s ready to swack its —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: You don’t want to make a saltwater crocodile mad, do you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: No.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Twin-spotted Sphinx Moth</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/05/23/twin-spotted-sphinx-moth/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/05/23/twin-spotted-sphinx-moth/</id>
    <published>2015-05-23T08:40:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-05-23T11:12:38-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-05-23-twin-spotted-sphinx-moth-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Tell us what is this moth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Sphinx!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: There’s about a thousand kinds of sphinx moths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: &lt;em&gt;Yay!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Maybe a walnut sphinx, I think it’s probably a walnut sphinx, because there’s lots of
walnut trees around it. Let me get the moth book. [Leaves room]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Do you think it just hatched out of its little cocoon? I miss that little peeper…
[Does a little beat boxing] Yay! Miles came back!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: A twin-spotted sphinx.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: It’s probably that…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: No that’s a small eyed sphinx.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Thought it was a giant sphinx. Is it a giant sphinx?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: No giant sphinx is… they’re much bigger. They look sort of like a rustic sphinx except…
or they look like a tomato hornworm with yellow underwings, except about that big… It’s
probably either from a poplar, apple or birch, I think. One of those trees. Probably poplar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Any salient points about the twin-spotted sphinx moth?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Uh yeah, I got a point. Why did it poo on our white paper?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: That’s a question, not a point. Why is it shaking its wings?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: All moths do that if they haven’t flown in a long time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: They’re warming up?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yeah. Especially tent caterpillar moths. They have such small wings that they can’t fly
without warming up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Really? I did not know that about moths. So they really rely on their camouflage,
‘cos they can’t just fly away if they need to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: They can, but if they haven’t flown for a day they have to warm up their wings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Why would they not fly for a day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: I know… some don’t. There was that catalpa sphinx that we saw, and it had to warm its
wings up before flying. Probably been sitting there for about one or two days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Well it makes it handy for moth analysis…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Remember how Miles found an imperial moth at a gas station?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Mmm-hmm, and there was a royal walnut moth —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles and India: [together, musically] &lt;em&gt;winnng&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: — and a dead Polyphemus moth, another squished imperial moth, and some cecropia moths…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: All at one gas station?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Gas station people don’t really like moths around. Even the most exciting and beautiful
ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What do gas station people like around?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: They just like around traffic and honks. Daddy did you know that atlas moths have to
flap their wings so much time before flying because they have such a big body? So they have to
go like this [flaps and pants] … or like this [flaps and pants again]. This is how the boys fly
[flaps and pants seriously]. This is how the girls fly [flaps and pants gracefully].&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Ah very gracefully the girls…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: The boys fly very serious-like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: No they actually don’t have a really big body. They should probably have a royal walnut
moth sized body, but their body is about half that size. But they have really big wings. So
they’re big muscly guys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Yeah? I wanna be a big muscly guy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: There was once a picture of one scaring away a crow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Really? Atlas moth?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yeah, and it was a really big one about that big.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: How big is the biggest butterfly ever?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Mmm, it’s the same size, exactly the same size, except the caterpillar is bigger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Oohhh-kay…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What’s the biggest one called?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Mmm, Queen Alexandra’s birdwing, I think.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Queen Alexander’s bird wing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yeah a weird name.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Queeland Aglandis bird fling?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Who was queen… Queen of Atlantis bird wing? Who was Queen Alexander?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Sometimes They Hang Around the Moon</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/05/22/sometimes-they-hang-around-the-moon/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/05/22/sometimes-they-hang-around-the-moon/</id>
    <published>2015-05-22T07:23:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-05-22T19:46:13-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-05-22-sometimes-they-hang-around-the-moon-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: This is a luna moth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: And a leaf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah, it’s a leaf. It’s on the forest floor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Do their heads look like that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yes, they have big round heads with these small, fluffy antennas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: How big does a luna moth get?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Well… it usually depends on which is a female and which is a male, because the female
usually gets bigger, but the male, he stays smaller, because he doesn’t really lay eggs, so
they just stay put.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: They just hang around?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah they just don’t really do the laying eggs part. They just —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: The boys do the hunting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: &lt;em&gt;Nnnoo,&lt;/em&gt; boy luna moths don’t hunt, they just —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: The boy eagles do the hunting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: We’re not talking about eagles in this interview, Taj. But anyway. The boys usually come
out in a light when nobody’s around because they’re really shy moths. It’s really uncommon to
see them if they’re around while people are around, because they just don’t really like being
around when somebody else is around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: When people are around?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah they mostly like a bit more quiet, so they go somewhere else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Where do they go for quiet?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Well they go somewhere where there’s lights on, or sometimes they hang around the moon,
on a big tree or something. But if somebody left their light on, and there’s nobody around, the
luna moths, they just fly over to sit on the windowsill, unless somebody scares them. And if
you go outside and look, you’ll see that it’s flown away, leaving a little bit of green wing
dust on the window.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Just Walking Under a Giant Flower</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/05/20/just-walking-under-a-giant-flower/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/05/20/just-walking-under-a-giant-flower/</id>
    <published>2015-05-19T20:11:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-05-22T19:46:13-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-05-20-just-walking-under-a-giant-flower-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Thisss… is a picture of Miles just walking under a giant flower, because he’s been
shrunken, and now he’s just walking around looking for a carrot, because he bought himself a pet
were-rabbit, and he’s looking for a carrot to give to it, so he’s just walking around trying to
tell which one’s a carrot or not, and he needs his were-rabbit to help him, and his were-rabbit
is trailing behind…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A Picture of Two Rabbits</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/05/18/a-picture-of-two-rabbits/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/05/18/a-picture-of-two-rabbits/</id>
    <published>2015-05-18T07:57:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-05-22T19:46:13-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-05-18-a-picture-of-two-rabbits-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: This is a picture of two rabbits. This guy doesn’t really like this guy because… and this
guy doesn’t really like this guy because he’s kind of mean, and really naughty. But these are
rabbits… they live together but they don’t really like each other. It’s kind of like  &lt;em&gt;Ren
and Stimpy&lt;/em&gt;, they’re very fond of each other but they get mad at each other. They give each
other  spankings —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: They do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah if they do something wrong, like to the meals, or what they’re going to sit on, or
to the furniture…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: I can think of a couple other people like that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Mmm-hmm…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: How come they have four arms and two legs each?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: ‘Cos Taji really wanted four arms, because he wanted them to have twice the smack in
their arms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
