<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>samadhiBot</title>
  <subtitle>samadhiBot ministry of information</subtitle>
  <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/</id>
  <link href="http://one.samadhibot.com/"/>
  <link href="http://one.samadhibot.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2015-09-29T15:11:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>समाधिBot</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Pegasussed!</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/09/29/pegasussed/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/09/29/pegasussed/</id>
    <published>2015-09-29T15:11:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-09-29T16:00:21-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-09-29-pegasussed-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[Break in tape]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: &lt;em&gt;You just ruined the whole interview!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: We have enough time because daddy’s phone is at 100%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Okay we’re gonna do a do-over. &lt;em&gt;Take two!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: This is a picture of Zahra riding a unicorn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: No, unicorns have a unicorn hood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Okay it’s a pegasus. It’s got a nice little beard… curly hair on its wing —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: That’s hair on its wing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah. Actually no, that’s just the wing part.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: When are we going to get to the turtle?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Okay… this looks like a kind of tortoise. It has a hard shell and square shapes on its 
shell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: These are gooses, this is the sun, this is a flying pegasussed with Zahra on its back…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: All horses… all pegasusses fly, Taji.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: And a cat. And a turtle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Turtles don’t fly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: (The turtle is not in the drawing. The turtle is a toy that exists outside the 
drawing.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Okay let’s get back to the interview. It has a nice little curly mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[Break in tape]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Stop ruining the interviews, mommy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Will you tell us about the pegasus’ fancy wings?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: It has nice curly patterns on its wings. Zahra wanted a flower right here, and a little 
curl right here. And there’s this nice patch of white.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Why does everything have reptilian eyes? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: I don’t know, that’s just the new trendy style. Next time they’re gonna have ‘X’ eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: What’s up with its mouth, why is it like a candy cane? Or a walking stick?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Because, Zahra wanted curly mouths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: It’s smiling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yes. That’s another reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Anything else?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yes. This cat is opening its mouth, because it’s saying, “Rawwwrrr!” Because that’s what 
cats sound like when they’re screaming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: The cat has been dropped by the hawk and is falling from the sky?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: It’ll land on its feet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah. I think so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Why are the geese floating in midair?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: No they’re not, they’re flapping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Why are their legs on the ground, and they only have one wing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Because I couldn’t make room for two?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: Sure you could, you could just go like this… &lt;em&gt;mmm-hmm…&lt;/em&gt; and make a wing right here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: &lt;em&gt;Not on its neck, Taj!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: Two hundred plus two hundred…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Shh, we’re not doing maths right now. Anyway, Zahra is not really in a good mood right 
now…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zahra: &lt;em&gt;Three hundred, fat head!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>This Is My Space House</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/08/26/this-is-my-space-house/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/08/26/this-is-my-space-house/</id>
    <published>2015-08-26T17:14:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-09-29T16:00:21-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-08-26-this-is-my-space-house-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: This is my space house.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: A space house in space?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Mm-hmm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Is it on a planet or is it floating in space?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: It’s floating in space.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Are these houses?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: No, that’s a mushroom. Actually that’s my spaceship. But he’s trying to take over it. 
He’s an evil guy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: He has… what’s that… a hat with a flower pot on it? He’s not a good guy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: No.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Looks like he’s getting attacked by —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah that’s Space Woobie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Is that a space chihuahua?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah, that’s Woobie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Love that!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: He thought that this thing was a space blueberry, even though it's really a space bomb, 
disguised as a blueberry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Oh my! Who’s this other person in the background?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: That’s me. That’s my house, and someone keeps getting into it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Is that your house or your spaceship?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Well… this is my spaceship, that’s my house.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Oh okay. And what’s going on back here? Is that part of your house?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah, it’s trails. There’s my mailbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Are these windows in the mountains?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Mm-hmm. And right now I’m running to stop this guy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: And then is there… a dragon in the sky?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah I call it the thin-nosed dragon. It kind of keeps the sun away… Yeah it’s kind of   
the guard, but today it’s not really watching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Yeah this guy got in…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Zahra drew a little space pond of pink. She did a nice job on that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Mm-hmm. I thought that was maybe a space potato, but it’s a space pond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah. There’s the door which kind of… well, I call this my Square Area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What happens in the Square Area?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: It’s usually just… oh my Square Area… is where I do &lt;em&gt;things important…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Even though there’s a bad guy who’s getting chewed on by a space chihuahua, everyone 
looks pretty happy. It seems like a pretty happy place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yes. There’s one reason why there’s this big boundary: so no one goes floating off. 
That’s the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Is there gravity here, or do you bounce like a trampoline when you run in this place? 
Or is it just like on Earth?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: You just kind of bounce like you’re on a bunch of trampolines. But right now I'm on the 
ground, standing, staring at this guy. And I’m looking at Woobie also.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Only Space Woobie seems kind of serious about what he’s doing. Good morning, Miles!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: I’ve been up for an hour…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Yeah?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yes…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Well, good morning anyway…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Do you have any drawings that you want to do an interview about?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: No…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Okay…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: You scribbled all over my drawings…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Uh, no I didn’t —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yes you did, you scribbled all over them with permanent marker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Mutated Next Year Page</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/08/17/the-mutated-next-year-page/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/08/17/the-mutated-next-year-page/</id>
    <published>2015-08-17T15:52:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-09-29T16:00:21-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-08-17-the-mutated-next-year-page-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: &lt;em&gt;Boop.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Okay, this is the mutated next year page.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Oh wow!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: This is Taji…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Uh huh… Taji looks like a demonic bug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yes. This is Zahra.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: She looks like a mosquito.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: She kind of is a mosquito.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Okay, is Miles on here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah Miles is that mosquito.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: How do you feel about that, Miles?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Not that good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: And there’s Woobie. He’s a man-eating barker dog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: I’m just happy that I’m not that guy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: You’re happy that you’re not Taj?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: He looks kind of like a mutated potato.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Alright let’s be nice to mutated-potato-Taj.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: This is me, and that’s daddy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Dad looks terrifyingly happy. What am I so happy about? That I didn’t have to be a 
mosquito? Is mom on here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: She’s that guy… lady.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Lady, yeah. And then there’s the sun…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah that’s Uncle David.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: That’s Uncle David! And what’s up here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: That’s the moon. He’s smiling in the background.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: And what about these orbs back there?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Well, they’re mad. They’re chasing him, but he doesn’t notice. Because he’s going around 
in circles. He’s pacing…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What are these though?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: They’re little stars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: They’re stars chasing the moon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Mmm-hmm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: But stars are millions of times bigger than any normal sized moon… usually…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: &lt;em&gt;“That's no moon. It's a space station.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Mmm uh-kay…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What is this writing all about?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Well, I just put that there for the fun of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Yeah? Your hand writing is pretty good. &lt;em&gt;“Skamizzic skitpwit to you eeskt.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: What’s this guy saying?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: &lt;em&gt;“Meat kips.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Taj is saying, &lt;em&gt;“Eh tissuah… Ketita.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Anyway, that’s someone else’s fridge, and Woobie’s totally scavenging off everything   
except for half of a bone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Ha! And he’s looking back at that half bone, thinking, “Maybe I’d like to go back 
for some more.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Okay, the other side…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-08-17-the-mutated-next-year-page-2-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: These are a bunch of guys that have been filled up with blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Oh yeah? Aren’t all guys kind of filled up with blood?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Um, yes, but these guys really like being like that, so they just kind of turned red.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: And tell me about the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah… I let Taj draw this part. I drew this for Taji so that he could give it to you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-08-17-the-mutated-next-year-page-3-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What about this part?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: That’s Taj and that’s bald you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: That’s bald me?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Actually bald Taji and hairy you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: I think hairy Taj and bald me is closer to the truth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: You’re so creepy daddy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: In real life, or in this drawing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: In that drawing. You’re a weirdo without a beard-o.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: You’ve got giant eyes…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: I like that heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah Taji decorated it a lot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Taj decorated that? I like his decorations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Speaking of Taj, did you make mommy coffee?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: No, ‘cos she’s not awake yet. What does Taj have to do with coffee?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Hut Hay Hen Hike</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/08/13/hut-hay-hen-hike/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/08/13/hut-hay-hen-hike/</id>
    <published>2015-08-13T12:52:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-09-29T16:00:21-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-08-13-hut-hay-hen-hike-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: We’re doing an interview on the letter ‘H’. I know one thing about it: it’s respectable 
to feed animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Oh yeah?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Mmm-hmm. Well, if you’ve got an animal, and you never feed it, that’s not good to do. 
Another thing is, if you see a stranger, you’re really not a'sposed to &lt;em&gt;mess with it…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: What — what did you say?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Well you’re not really supposed to mess with anybody if they’re a stranger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Yeah… wait… &lt;em&gt;mess with their mind??&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: No, you know, &lt;em&gt;talk to them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Oh, okay… right… um… okay. Taji, what’s in the picture? Can you see a letter ‘H’?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: I can!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: Yes, I can. It’s on the house.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What color is the ‘H’?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India &amp; Taj: White.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: The chicken matches the color of the ‘H’. Another thing: the door looks like a pancake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: &lt;em&gt;It’s a pancake door!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: But another thing about it: the girls did a good job. Usually you’re supposed to leave 
when you see a stranger, but instead they made a meal for him —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: Hey daddy you did awesome trees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Thanks, Taj! India, do you want to tell the story behind this picture? You don’t have 
to tell the whole story, but tell generally what happened. I know that there was a hut, and
there were three girls, and a creepy stranger, but I don’t know all of what happened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: I know one part of it. It’s kind of the end part. The girls all went to sleep, except 
the wise one, which kind of thought, &lt;em&gt;“Oh! I have to feed the animals!”&lt;/em&gt; The other girls,
they just went to sleep, and old stranger dude locked them in the cellar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: &lt;em&gt;Dear me…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: But the girl who fed the animals, it’s kind of like a thing. You know, like a test? When 
you get a punishment for not doing something. Well why didn’t he tell them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Why indeed!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Another thing: there’s something kind of &lt;em&gt;suspecting&lt;/em&gt; about the fire. Not 
everyone  who just lives in the middle of nowhere knows how to light a fire. So maybe he knew
how to make food… but the girls just kind of did it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Yeah… if you know how to make a fire, presumably you could make at least something 
simple enough to —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Like an egg —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Like an egg. Something simple enough to feed the animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: And the chicken — Taj, stop messing with the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Are you gonna split, Taj?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: Mommy said it’s lunch time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: The ‘H’ looks good because the chimney. In one part of the ‘H’ it goes up through the 
roof to the chimney. I thought the rest of the ‘H’ was just going to go up out of the chimney.
And this background part is like a Christmas tree —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: Hey guys it’s time to have lunch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Anyway that looks like Christmas has already gone past. And he had a Christmas tree but 
then he planted it somewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: True dat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: And the roof looks like hay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Yep. And he’s having a fire inside his hut with a straw roof, which I don’t think I 
would do, but I guess in Scandinavian countries they do that. Seems dodgy to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Small Eyed Sphinx Moth</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/08/03/small-eyed-sphinx-moth/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/08/03/small-eyed-sphinx-moth/</id>
    <published>2015-08-03T11:15:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-09-29T16:00:21-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-08-03-small-eyed-sphinx-moth-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What is it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Small eyed sphinx.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: And where did you find it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Back porch? It was just sitting on one of the stairs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: &lt;em&gt;Ohh!&lt;/em&gt; That was a cocoon that I hatched!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Wow!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Where’d you find the —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: — cocoon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: I didn’t find the cocoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: You found the egg?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: No.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot &amp;amp; India: &lt;em&gt;You found the caterpillar?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: No.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Then what —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: — did you find?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: I found a moth, and it laid eggs, and then they hatched into caterpillars, and then they 
formed cocoons, and then there were moths. I released all of them but this one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Crazy… wow… you’re kind of a mother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-08-03-small-eyed-sphinx-moth-2-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: When did you find this moth’s mother?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Where did you find her?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: I was walking in the woods, and then it fell on my head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: It fell on your head?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: This moth’s own mother fell on your head? Wow…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: I’ve got a question: why does it have a waggly tail?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: That subspecies of sphinx moths usually have curved tails. And its underwings stick out 
beyond its top wings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Do these fly well?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yes, almost all sphinx moths are really strong flyers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Its body looks so big in comparison to its wings, it seems like it would have a hard 
time flying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-08-03-small-eyed-sphinx-moth-3-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Someone found a pink spotted sphinx twenty miles off the coast of Georgia… yes I think 
it was Georgia… yes. It flew out to sea twenty-five miles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Wow, they found it on their boat, or they found it on an island?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: It landed on their boat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: You know those brown and pink things? At the side of its wings? What are they?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: That’s the side of its wings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: I know, that’s what I’m talking about. What are they?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: The side of its wings! The side of its wings are the side of its wings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Okay… the side of its wings are the side of its wings…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: That red line on it looks almost like a mohawk. See its underwings stick out? That 
particular species usually does that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Those things… those pink and brown things.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Those are just pigments in its wings. You’re talking complete nonsense, India.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>What is not to like about Wasps, Mosquitos and Yellow Jackets?</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/07/29/what-is-not-to-like-about-wasps-mosquitos-and-yellow-jackets/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/07/29/what-is-not-to-like-about-wasps-mosquitos-and-yellow-jackets/</id>
    <published>2015-07-29T11:36:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-07-29T11:59:20-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-07-29-what-is-not-to-like-about-wasps-mosquitos-and-yellow-jackets-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What’s this one?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: It’s about how much I do not like wasps, mosquitos and yellow jackets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What is not to like about wasps, mosquitos and yellow jackets?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Well, sometimes when you’re swimming and yellow jackets fall in the water, they sting 
you just to hold on, instead of grabbing on. And that’s what happened to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: You got stung in the water by a yellow jacket?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yep. That’s why I don’t like yellow jackets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: You know, I don’t think they do it to hold on. I think they do it just to be mean.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah. The reason why I don’t like wasps is because one stung Miles. And when you’re 
minding your own business, sitting down or standing up, they just sting you for no reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: I got stung by a dead wasp when I was little. Could you imagine stinging someone
after you’re already dead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: No… The reason why I don’t like mosquitos is because you’re always minding your business 
when you get bitten by one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Is that one half full or half empty?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Half full.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Half full of blood?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah, I could only draw the thing like that because… well you know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
