<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>samadhiBot</title>
  <subtitle>samadhiBot ministry of information</subtitle>
  <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/</id>
  <link href="http://one.samadhibot.com/"/>
  <link href="http://one.samadhibot.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2015-08-03T11:15:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>समाधिBot</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Small Eyed Sphinx Moth</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/08/03/small-eyed-sphinx-moth/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/08/03/small-eyed-sphinx-moth/</id>
    <published>2015-08-03T11:15:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-08-03T11:52:22-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-08-03-small-eyed-sphinx-moth-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What is it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Small eyed sphinx.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: And where did you find it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Back porch? It was just sitting on one of the stairs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: &lt;em&gt;Ohh!&lt;/em&gt; That was a cocoon that I hatched!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Wow!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Where’d you find the —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: — cocoon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: I didn’t find the cocoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: You found the egg?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: No.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot &amp;amp; India: &lt;em&gt;You found the caterpillar?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: No.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Then what —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: — did you find?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: I found a moth, and it laid eggs, and then they hatched into caterpillars, and then they 
formed cocoons, and then there were moths. I released all of them but this one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Crazy… wow… you’re kind of a mother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-08-03-small-eyed-sphinx-moth-2-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: When did you find this moth’s mother?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Where did you find her?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: I was walking in the woods, and then it fell on my head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: It fell on your head?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: This moth’s own mother fell on your head? Wow…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: I’ve got a question: why does it have a waggly tail?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: That subspecies of sphinx moths usually have curved tails. And its underwings stick out 
beyond its top wings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Do these fly well?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yes, almost all sphinx moths are really strong flyers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Its body looks so big in comparison to its wings, it seems like it would have a hard 
time flying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-08-03-small-eyed-sphinx-moth-3-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Someone found a pink spotted sphinx twenty miles of the coast of Georgia… yes I think it 
was Georgia… yes. It flew out to sea twenty-five miles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Wow, they found it on their boat, or they found it on an island?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: It landed on their boat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: You know those brown and pink things? At the side of its wings? What are they?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: That’s the side of its wings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: I know, that’s what I’m talking about. What are they?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: The side of its wings! The side of its wings are the side of its wings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Okay… the side of its wings are the side of its wings…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: That red line on it looks almost like a mohawk. See its underwings stick out? That 
particular species usually does that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Those things… those pink and brown things.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Those are just pigments in its wings. You’re talking complete nonsense, India.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>What is not to like about Wasps, Mosquitos and Yellow Jackets?</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/07/29/what-is-not-to-like-about-wasps-mosquitos-and-yellow-jackets/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/07/29/what-is-not-to-like-about-wasps-mosquitos-and-yellow-jackets/</id>
    <published>2015-07-29T11:36:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-07-29T11:59:20-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-07-29-what-is-not-to-like-about-wasps-mosquitos-and-yellow-jackets-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What’s this one?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: It’s about how much I do not like wasps, mosquitos and yellow jackets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What is not to like about wasps, mosquitos and yellow jackets?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Well, sometimes when you’re swimming and yellow jackets fall in the water, they sting 
you just to hold on, instead of grabbing on. And that’s what happened to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: You got stung in the water by a yellow jacket?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yep. That’s why I don’t like yellow jackets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: You know, I don’t think they do it to hold on. I think they do it just to be mean.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah. The reason why I don’t like wasps is because one stung Miles. And when you’re 
minding your own business, sitting down or standing up, they just sting you for no reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: I got stung by a dead wasp when I was little. Could you imagine stinging someone
after you’re already dead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: No… The reason why I don’t like mosquitos is because you’re always minding your business 
when you get bitten by one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Is that one half full or half empty?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Half full.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Half full of blood?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah, I could only draw the thing like that because… well you know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Katydid</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/07/21/katydid/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/07/21/katydid/</id>
    <published>2015-07-20T20:38:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-07-21T10:25:57-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-07-21-katydid-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: A katydid is a five-legged insect that’s kind of like a grasshopper —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: It’s six-legged, that one just lost its leg. Sometimes their back legs fall off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Why would their back legs fall off?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: I don’t know, they’re just not attached that well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: They do it for defense, like if a wasp egg was clinging on it, you know —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Uhh, no they don’t, they don’t really do it for defense —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: You know how those sea star things —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: No, it’s not like that. They sometimes get their leg snagged… and then their leg falls 
off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: And they’re not injured at all…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;div class="image"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-07-21-katydid-3-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What do these guys eat?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Leaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Leaves exclusively? They wouldn’t eat an aphid if one came along?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Grass… things like that. Things like grasshoppers eat, they seem to have a grasshopper 
diet. Except they seem to like leaves more. And sometimes they bite people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Really? So they would eat an aphid?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yeah maybe. And look, they have tiny little antennae right there… and there… [pointing 
to the sides of its mouth]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Is it like a Komodo dragon that smells with its tongue?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: No.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: So it smells with its nose?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: It also has a weird plate-like thing on the tip of its nose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: This is what it does… [gestures]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Oh that’s its upper lip? What’s behind that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Underneath there’s… how am I gonna do this… [makes sideways chewing gestures]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Ah!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Like that… mandibles. And it looks just like a leaf. Its wings look just like a leaf. 
They even have veins to go with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;div class="image"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-07-21-katydid-2-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: Hey guys let’s just delete this one. This one isn’t good. This interview isn’t good —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: It’s never too late! Things can always turn around —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: How much more minutes? How much more minutes?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Um… we don’t know. You never know how long an interview is gonna go. But I edit 
heavily…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: So we get out all of the poo talk —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Yes, any mention of poo gets removed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: I know one thing about them: they’re like praying mantises, they lick their legs all the 
time. And if you look closely at the skin it looks like jelly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: It looks like bubbly green candy jelly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: And someone might want to eat this one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Oh yeah, and its little hand! It’s got a hook at the end, what does it do with its 
hook?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: I think it just sits around with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>You Say sɪˈkeɪdə and I’ll Say sɪˈkɑːdə</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/07/16/you-say-cicada-and-ill-say-cicada/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/07/16/you-say-cicada-and-ill-say-cicada/</id>
    <published>2015-07-16T14:20:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-07-16T14:37:27-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-07-16-you-say-cicada-and-ill-say-cicada-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What do you know about cicadas?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Miles, what do you know about cicadas?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: What do &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; know about cicadas?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: They make ear splitting sounds?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Why do they do that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: I dunno, to attract a mate or something?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Is it a female trying to attract a male, or a male trying to attract a female?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: I guess a male?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: They usually make the earsplitting noises while they’re eating. I don’t know why, but 
they drink sap at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: India doesn’t know about any cicadas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: And they’ve got giant eyeballs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Can they see well?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: They have pretty good eyesight. They’re not like a dragonfly or a mantis shrimp. Mantis 
shrimps can see about seventeen times better than humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: &lt;em&gt;Really?!!&lt;/em&gt; Mantis shrimps?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yes. They also sit in holes, and when divers poke at them they smash off their fingers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: &lt;em&gt;Good lawd!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: They don’t bite them off, it’s just the force of it, they go like that [gestures] and 
their pincer travels out at about 500 miles per hour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;div class="image"&gt;&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-07-16-you-say-cicada-and-ill-say-cicada-2-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Do these guys have a mouth?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: No, they have a little sucky thing squished against their neck, and then they up-stretch 
it and stab it into a tree, and suck its blood, basically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Could they do that to a person?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: No.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Are you sure? I was a little freaked out by this little guy when I was taking his 
picture. ‘These any relation to a locust?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: I don’t really know, but I’m pretty sure that they’re basically a giant spittle bug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Don’t those spittle bugs have a seventh appendage —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: A gear. A naturally forming gear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: A naturally forming gear — am I thinking of a spittle bug?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: These don’t have anything like that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yes but they do fly in much the same way. And they have the same sort of shape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: They have kind of like a hammerhead shark head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yeah, and they look like they have mustaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Do they have a mustache?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Mmm, I dunno, I think it’s just antennae right below their nose and their mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Have you seen how the head looks kind of like a hammerhead shark’s head?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Yeah we were just talking about that. And right at the bottom of the wings they’re 
bright green.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Where do cicadas overwinter? Are they eggs then? Are they grubs?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: I’m not really sure. The ones that come out every seventeen years —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Isn’t that locusts?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: No cicadas, it’s a variety of cicada. Those ones grow insanely slowly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: And they’re underground for all that time, right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miles: Mmm-hmm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Origin of Geeses</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/07/13/the-origin-of-geeses/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/07/13/the-origin-of-geeses/</id>
    <published>2015-07-13T06:10:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-07-16T14:32:21-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-07-13-the-origin-of-geeses-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Why is the egg so big? Usually goose eggs are much smaller than that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: It’s kind of the storybook golden egg. I was thinking about that a lot while I was
drawing it. It’s not realistic is it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Mmm…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: But the goose is always sitting on a preposterously large golden egg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Like the queen ant is always sitting there laying eggs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Have you ever drawn a goose?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yes… a baby goose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Do you know what a baby goose is called?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: … a gooseling?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: A &lt;em&gt;gosling&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Bother…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: I once got chased by a goose. Ever been chased by a goose?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Is it scary?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: It is!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Well… they are big honking gooses…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: They lift their heads up high and spread their wings and hiss, and all of a sudden 
they go from being something not much different from a duck or a chicken… to this terrifying
once-was-a-dinosaur thing chasing after you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: But I’ve been chased by a bull before, in India.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Well that’s a lot scarier. How’d you get chased by a bull?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Remember? We got a bit too close. That was scary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: I don’t think that was a bull though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: What was it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: It was a cow. Yeah the bulls are like a ton of rippling muscle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: It went like this… remember?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: It was doing that thing with its hoof…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: The hoofy thing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Mm-hmm. Do you know the story of the goose laying the golden egg?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Jack and the Beanstalk? Uh… &lt;em&gt;yeah&lt;/em&gt;. I’ve seen that show before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Is there any other story of a goose laying a golden egg, or is Jack and the Beanstalk
the only one?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: I guess it’s the only one. There’s a Puss ’n Boots version of it, and there’s a mommy
goose that’s the size of a house, or a &lt;em&gt;Titanoboa&lt;/em&gt;. Early birds had teeth, daddy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Yeah?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah. They just had tiny little nubbin teeth. And early birds looked like penguins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: &lt;em&gt;Really?!!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah, &lt;em&gt;rrreally&lt;/em&gt; big fluffy penguins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: [Laughs] I thought early birds were dinosaurs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: They were, but they were big, fluffy looking penguins. [Makes crashing sounds like
giant dino-penguin feet stomping] And there’s this kind with flippers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: I wonder if that’s how the birds survived when other dinosaurs did not. Maybe there
was some kind of… what’s the word…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Safety ground? A safe coral spot?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: An intervention! Maybe there was an intervention where they said, these other
dinosaurs, the &lt;em&gt;Spinosauruses&lt;/em&gt; and whatnot, things with spikes and clubs… we’re going to
let them burn. But these big soft, fluffy penguin-like dinosaurs are just too cute to let get
wiped out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Oh by the way, they were this big. [gestures]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: About… four feet high?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Mm-hmm, that’s a really big fluffy penguin. The kind with flippers is only this big.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: You know if we could clone one of those big fluffy dino-penguins, we could make a
&lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt;  of money…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah… they’re really fluffy… they’re this fluffy —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Wow, mostly fluff?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah, the females can get to this fluffy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Really? Were they just adorably fluffy, or were they also cold blooded killers?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: At that time they were just vegetarians. They were just curious, they would come here,
eat a bit, go to another spot, eat a bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: That sounds nice…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah. They didn’t really have to worry about swimming, because of all their fluff, it
just made them float.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Could they fly then?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Nope. At that time they could kind of fly if it got really windy, then they would just
go  up in the air —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Like a tumbleweed!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah, like a tumbleweed! Anyway, how did you draw the G into the goose?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: I drew the letter G very lightly first, and then I looked for a goose to draw around
it. So I could see the body of a goose, mostly inside the letter G, and I could imagine the head
of the goose at the end of the top of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Those big fluffy penguins, they had &lt;em&gt;lonnng&lt;/em&gt; pointy beaks. Yeah like that…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Was it a specific species of big fluffy penguins, or there were lots of different
kinds?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: It was two kinds of them. I don’t know the names of them, but I called the one that we
were first talking about the tumbleweed. The next one is kind of skinny, so I call it the naked
bird.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: The naked bird?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah, it doesn’t really have many feathers. It just has big feathers it walks around in.
They’re funny.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Alright… penguin interview!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: And goose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Oh yeah, goose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Fishes and Dolphins and Sharks</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/06/29/fishes-and-dolphins-and-sharks/"/>
    <id>http://one.samadhibot.com/2015/06/29/fishes-and-dolphins-and-sharks/</id>
    <published>2015-06-29T11:32:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2015-06-29T11:49:18-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>समाधिBot</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;img src="/images/posts/2015-06-29-fishes-and-dolphins-and-sharks-small.jpg" /&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: That’s a spotty dolphin. That’s a killer whale… hammerhead shark… great white shark, and
nurse shark, and that’s an eel. That’s one of those tiger fishies — but I forgot the long
scraggly things.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: They’re tiger sharks. Tiger sharks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah tiger sharks. I mean lion sharks —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: Lionfish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Yeah lionfish. There’s a little… minnow… minnow — yeah minnow. This is a micro-minnow —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: India, did you draw… a box shark?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: There’s no such thing as a box shark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;समाधिBot: What’s this funny looking one?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: Um, it’s this kind of large lumpy thing that lurks in the deep. I forgot to draw the
ginormous teeth on it, because it has ginormous teeth. And I forgot to draw the lure thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: You forgot to draw the shark whale also.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: I couldn’t fit it on there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taj: Because shark whales are —&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India: &lt;em&gt;Anywayyy&lt;/em&gt;… this is a piranha — this is called a red bellied piranha. That’s ummm…
that’s a catfish — yeah a catfish, and that’s a butterfly fish. &lt;em&gt;Annnd&lt;/em&gt;, is that all of
them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
